I looked cool
Я смотрел прикольно
that I looked about me
что смотрел про меня
back there that you remember what videos you remember with me
еще там что помнишь какие ролики со мной
I knew right away that you were for the war or
Я тебе сразу знал то ты за войну или
against
против
killing unequivocally I don’t hear Nani
убивать не слышу Нани
I’m already killing
Я уже убиваю
just in front of you I smeared one fascist
только что перед тобой одного фашиста
So he probably hangs himself
размазал Так что он наверное повеситься
everything is clear you’ll take the machine gun  or maybe,
все понятно автомат возьмешь а может
for example, if they drive you to Ukraine,
Например если тебя пригонит в Украину
shoot you a biscuit of gnawing
стрельнуть тебя бисквита выгрызения
conscience, absolutely
совести абсолютно
if you look if a person is driven here
если смотри если человека пригонят сюда
by an occupier,
оккупанта
maybe not just
может не просто
you are against the war, but not just like that
ты против войны но не просто так
Come here Tell me your versions
Приходим сюда Расскажи мне свои версии
of the red one Why do you Come here
красненький Зачем же вы Приходите сюда
to our land
на землицу нашу
so that there would be no you  they ask you
чтобы не было вас спрашивают вам
we help
помогаем
super yes we only have fascists Yes that you
супер да у нас только фашистов Да что
need to come to kill a bunch of people these
надо прийти убить кучу людей этих
fascists can’t be found but what is it you have
фашистов не найти а что же такое вы
already caught some fascists Well
каких-то фашистов уже поймали А ну
tell me boy
расскажи мальчик
if you were
если ты был
a guy like you would normally somehow
паренек типа ты бы нормально как-то
think while you think  like a boy
мысль пока ты мыслишь как мальчик
so let's
поэтому Давайте
you fought in Ukraine
ты воевал в Украине
[laughter]
[смех]
at least
хотя бы
world famous battle battle battle of
всемирно известно битва битва битва при
supermar  kete the battle of McDonald's
супермаркете битва при Макдональдс
I think it's
думаю так
not funny to you yourself
тебе самому не смешно
you're not funny to yourself no now no And
тебе не смешно самому нет сейчас нет А
where did you fight in
где ты воевал
Mariupol seriously The
Мариуполе серьезно
central street of Mariupol
Центральная улица Мариуполя
How did you coordinate your actions
А как ты координировал свои действия
where are you going
куда ты едешь
through What settlements did you
через Какие населенные пункты вы
stop by in Mariupol
заезжали в Мариуполь
maximum battle of McDonald's
максимум битва при Макдональдсе у тебя
did you have
была
every second one comes out, show
каждый второй выходит
me Show me on the phone show on the phone the
покажи давай Фотки покажи на телефон
pictures
покажи на телефоне фотки
opened on the phone Show how people
открылись на телефоне Покажи как люди
will show
покажет
your phone there
твой телефон есть
Yes it’s sad you
Да печально
don’t dare How to explain this I
так не смеешь Как это объяснить я
suffer repetition I heard
мучаюсь повторение услышал
so you don’t laugh I
так не смеешься
don’t hear the sound Well correction corrected there
не слышу звука Ну поправка поправ там
corrected the sound on the microphone on
поправ звук на микрофоне на телефоне
I can’t hear you on the phone if you hear me
я тебя не слышу если ты меня слышишь
touch the spirit so that I can hear me
дотронься духа чтобы я Ты слышишь меня
touch the spirit If you hear me, you
дотронься духа Если Слышишь вот ты меня
hear me Damn, I didn’t hear you
слышишь Блин я тебя не слышал [__] как
to look at you,
посмотреть
you saw yourself
ты видел себя
only as an airplane would dump  drop it like a
разве что как самолета бы сбрасывали как
bomb, it’s just the
бомбу просто
sky you know how a frame like
небо ты такой знаешь как рама типа тебя
throws you off
сбрасывает
That is, you’re sitting to me now you’re sitting shorter
То есть ты мне сейчас ты сидишь короче
near the refrigerator there you tell me something
возле холодильника там мне что-то
about a machine gun
расскажешь про автомат
Look, I find people
Смотри я нахожу нахожу таких людей
who are in Mariupol Yes And now I’m making
которые в Мариуполе Да И вот делаю
a portrait such that they
портрет такой что они
really freed  Mariupol, I’m making it
реально освобождали Мариуполь я делаю
like a gallery of Russian glory, well done,
как бы галерею русской славы
yes, but you got an order for Mariupol, they gave you a
молодец да А у вас орден дали вам за
medal, and in what area is
медаль дали а в какой области находится
Where is
Где находится
everything, let’s look Near McDonald’s, you
Все давай смотри Возле Макдональдса ты
won’t get any stars because
уже звездюлей не получишь потому что
McDonald’s left Russia, yes, but Be
Макдональдс ушел из России да но Будь
careful Come on Slava  Ukraine
осторожен Давай Слава Украине